SAUD KADIRI

<u>+91 8530085480</u> saudkadiri@gmail.com

Kismat Nagar, Kurla Mumbai-70

<u>LinkedIn</u>
<u>Github</u>
<u>Twitter</u>
saudkadiri.com

PROFILE

I'm specialised in the field of Artificial Intelligence (with Deep Learning being my specialised subset). I did my Computer Science from the prestigious University of Mumbai in which Computer Science and Mathematics were my core subjects. I'm well experienced in working on Blockchain, XR, System Programs(Compilers/OS) and also AWS/GCP. I also am an enthusiast Competitive Programmer and have studied the core concepts of Problem Solving and Algorithms throughly.

EXPERIENCE

Google DSC, Technical Manager — 2021-22

was the technical manager of my college's GDSC for the year 2021-22 and a Core team member. In this role, I developed syllabus and designed programs and solutions that were to be taught to the participants attending the workshops. I also was the Cloud Facilitator, in which 164 students participated and I conducted sessions, introducing them Google Cloud. In this process I was taught Google Cloud by Google Engineers themselves. I led a team of two members under me and we had a good bond in making all the "Technical" stuff work. I developed syllabus and programs for- Web development, Flutter (Dart), Python and other Workshops.

WebVisit Monitor, Software Lead — 2021-22

This extension was designed for monitoring negativity, we used sentiment analysis to detect distasteful content and marked the website as negative. Also each sentences were highlighted green, yellow and red as per their sentiment score. As the software lead for this project I was responsible for all the frameworks and technologies that were to be used by the system; We used tensorflow.js for Sentiment Analysis, Chart.js for graphical representation of the analysis. We applied RAD SDLC in a group of 4 members.

Online Voting System, Project lead — 2020-21

We developed an Online Voting system that was had all the security features including encryption; so as to keep the user information encrypted and also no manipulation of system was ensured.

Project Lead, Algorithm 6.0 — 2019-2019

I was the lead of a group of four in which we developed a Fake News Detector Android App and also a web app. The app was capable of allocating a unique id for each of the verified news based on web scrapping multiple sites.

EDUCATION

University of Mumbai, India — B.E. Computer Engineering, 2023

SKILLS

Languages: C/C++, Python, Swift, JavaScript

Frameworks: Django, Flask, Tensorflow, PyTorch, Keras, Svelte, NumPy,

Pandas, scikit-learn, opency, nltk, swiftui

Fields: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, System Programs